In today's video on Technical Mom YouTube Hindi channel,
we will learn how to do
Thought Party and Friends of ICC Lamp Board from your mobile, that is,
you do not need to know the story,
you can do insurance from your mobile,
so for this you have to go to
this page, the link of the speech will be
found in the description of the video and
after coming here you have to search your vehicle number,
enter it and your mobile
number and email ID,
after filing all these things you have to click on the gate,
like now when you click on the gate code, you will go to this
page, here you will
see two options, do you want first party
insurance or third party
insurance, the
amount will be charged and in third party a
fixed amount is charged, so we want third
party, so we will click on third party here,
like when we click on third party,
here we are seeing that our amount is being
written as 1374 rupees, so there is a
personal accidental tax here, if I remove it then it will be
reduced by one more, so if you
want to take personal accidental tax level then do
not remove it by checking otherwise you do
not want to take it  You
can make your insurance here only in 33, after that you have to
select your city here, so let me
select my city,
like Mau, Uttar Pradesh, after that
what to do, in
this way you can get insurance from your mobile, by making
payment through Google etc.,
now you will come like you will come to this page, here the
details of your bike will be
shown, which company's bike is it,
which model is it, after that the next
extra thing is why
update from KYC, in this
you will have to upload PAN card, Aadhar card document, so let's
click on begin KYC process,
here we will go to Aadhar card, then
here Aadhar card number, then full name,
click on verify,
what is the next step, your
engine number will become
100 here, after that you do not have to do anything here
and next from here you can make payment of Rs 845 using UPI or
from your wallet etc.
and your
policy will be downloaded immediately, so in what
way can you do your  Can we make it from mobile,
sir, can we do something like ICC
Lombard's two wheeler insurance, so
if you face any problem in making the insurance,
please comment, you will
definitely get a reply, so in this video
we told you how to make ICC Lombard's two
wheeler insurance third party,
exactly at any shop, but you
can make it from your mobile, so how did you like the video,
thank you from the heart for watching the entire video, and if
your page gets an error at any step, then
its next link
goes directly to your mobile or WhatsApp, by
clicking on it you will be
directed to that page